

## INFO

**N**a 7ab

7ahra Kirschblüte

Q

Address

Sorogatan 67 164 47 Stockholm



Phone

072-002 42 11



Mail

zahra.kirschblute@hotmail.com

in

Linkedin

https://tinyurl.com/kirschblute



Github

github.com/zahrakirschbluete/

## **PROFILE**

Full Stack Developer with previous experience in both the customer service and marketing departments of two of Sweden's fastest growing and sucessful e-commerces. My interest for coding sparked as a teenager and my current long term ambition is to continously grow as a developer.

### **TECH STACK**

C#, .Net Core, EF Core, MsSql, Blazor, JavaScript, React, Angular, HTML, SCSS, bootstrap and much more. I'm of course more than happy to learn new languages and frameworks in orde

# **LANGUAGES**



SWEDISH

Native tongue



**GERMAN**Native tongue



# ZAHRA KIRSCHBLÜTE FULL STACK DEVELOPER

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

2020-Present

#### **Meds Apotek AB**

Software Developer (intern)

- Developing in various projects using .NET Core, EF Core, Blazor, Blazorise and Azure Devops
- Creating intergration and unit tests using XUnit
- · Setting up and testing projects in stage server
- Writing powershell scripts

#### Snusbolaget AB

2019-2019

- Customer Service Manager
  - Optimized CS routines
- Set KPIs for the CS department
- · Directly reported to the CLO

#### Desenio AB

2018-2019

Marketing Coordinator, DACH market

- Had continious contact and successful collaborations with influencers
- Optimized routines to ensure that our influencers get the best possible service

#### Desenio AB

2017-2019

Senior Customer Service Coordinator, DACH market

- Set routines and upkept world-class customer service to ensure increased sales as a result
- · Worked with SEO to rank higher in search engines

#### Mcdonald´s Tornado

2016-2017

Shift Manager

• Responsible for the daily operations at the restaurant

# **EDUCATION**

2019-2021

Chas Academy:

Full Stack Web Development

Practical programme where we mainly focused on vanilla **JavaScript** and frameworks such as **React**, **Angular** and **NodeJs**. **HTML**, **CSS**, **PHP**, **UX Design**, **agile concepts** and much more were also a part of the programme.

2017-2017

McDonald's Business School:

Shift Manager Course

2015-2016

Stockholm Universiy:

Teacher Programme, German and English

2012-2015

St Eriks Gymnasium, Kungsholmen: Natural Science Programme